Hee-hee-hee-hee.
I'm so nervous!
I'm so nervous about the live beer delivery
Raw... Raw...
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous. Raw photos? Why do you call them "live photos"? What are photos that aren't live?
Hello. Nice to meet you. Good evening.
So this week's shift is Mariko. Mariko. Nice to meet you. It's been a long time.
What do you mean, "Mariko"? I think it's been February.
February was when I was still getting nosebleeds from all the Valentine's Day chocolates.
I didn't even get one!
Poor thing... it's all of a sudden...
Please don't do that.
My scars are all giggly...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's been six months.
Is it July now?
It's July.
July.
Today?
Today is July.
Well, well, well, well, it's not.
Okay, let's get back to the recording.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to begin.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, ma'am.
So today, we have the princess, the admiral, and the watchdog.
I look forward to working with you.
Watchdog.Number two.
We are Yoshimoto's classmates.
That's right.
You know, the other day, we used to drink a lot, and we would get some kaki no tane as a snack.
It's one of the most popular snacks.
There are just kaki no tane, kaki peas, and many other versions.
Wasabi...
Kaki-no-tane, I remember when I was a little girl, my grandma used to sell them in a can.
They used to come in square cans... with big kaki tane inside.
I see.
I wondered when they went on sale.
I'm a modern person, so I always turn to the Internet.
I was like, "Pop-pop-pop-pop-pop," and then I found out that he was the same age as me.
It was released in 1966.
It was released in 1966!
There were a lot of other classic products released in 1966 that are still on the market today.
Carl's.
I don't remember there still being a Carl's.
Yes, there is.
Carl's is gone.
It's gone...
Uncle Karl's gone.
I'm sure it's gone.
I loved the curry and cheese flavors.
That's right.
They're out of production.
But now...
It's still not sold in Kansai.
Only in Kansai?
So you moved to Kansai?
Good, good, good.Oh, good, good, good!
I envy people in Kansai.
It's good, isn't it?
Why?
By the way...
Pokey!
We were the same age.
The same age?
And... Sapporo Ichiban.
Noodle bag!
Sapporo Black Label
Sapporo Ichiban bagged noodles.
We were the same age.
Oh, really?
So I did some research.
Back then...
1966 is hard to imagine, isn't it?
Maybe his father or mother
I can't imagine what it must have been like back then.
That year...
That's the year I was born.
I was born a little bit.
I was born and then they started yelling at me, right?
Back then, right?
The three sacred treasures.
I mean, the Three Sacred Treasures...
Japanese mythologyOriginally a Japanese myth
It is an old myth
The gods made three treasures
There were three treasures.
The three sacred treasures, like swords or something weird like that.
That's where it came from, but that's not the original story.
But back then...
1966 was a time of rapid economic growth.
It was a period of rapid economic growth.
Japan's economy was booming.
Like China's economy today.
People could afford to buy all kinds of things at once.
People could afford to buy all kinds of things.
And the three most popular types of products for households at that time were
The 3C's: Color TV, Cooler, and Car.
a cooler, and a car.
Every family wanted to have all three of these things.
It's like they were saying, "Every family should have all three.
The popularity of the three types was originally a little more than 10 years ago.
TV, refrigerator, and washing machine.
Nowadays, there's almost no home without a TV, refrigerator, and washing machine.
At that time, everyone wanted one.
That's how it started.
Do you know what the popularity of the three types is these days?
I'm sure there are a lot of theories about this, but these are the three popular ones that are often referred to in this way.
The latest version, the very current smartphone.
No, no, no. Smart phones are probably a little older now.
Can I ask you something? Dishwasher.
You know, the one with the saralite automatic do-over? Everyone seems to want that one.
They all want that one.
Two of them. And one of them...Two of them are for "and feedback," and the other one is for, uh...
I don't have all three of these things at home, but I do have a robot vacuum cleaner.
Roomba... so it's a Roomba?
I think those are the three newest things people want, don't they?
Not so much.
Do you have a touch-tone machine in your house?
Yes, I do.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I thought you didn't have one.
Yes, it's common now.
By the way, it's quite recent.
The two of you were born in...
1999 and 2000, right?
A nostalgic hit product from each year.
Maybe this one, too.
For example, in 1999, there was i-mode.
I miss that cell phone from when it was still a "Galapagos" type.
What did you think of i-mode? It has an image of something like the Internet, doesn't it?
I used to say "i-mode, i-mode, i-mode" back then.
Like i-mode was in trouble.
And then there's ringtones.
Wow, a ringtone!
Beep-beep-beep.
What? Oh, my God.
What the hell is this?
Because the first thing in the game is Dance Dance Revolution.
Wow!
You know, the one where you stomp your feet like a chan-chan.
What's with the rush?
And then there's the buzzword, or rather the profession, charismatic hairdresser.
Charismatic hairdresser!Heh, charismatic hairdresser.
I don't know what to say.
He's an amazing hairdresser.
He's really good.
There are people who are nominated by celebrities, right?
He started getting a lot of attention in 1999.
Really?
I see.
People want to have their hair cut by him.
I'd like to see a lot of reservations.
And speaking of hit songs, the Three Dumpling Brothers...
Wow.
Three Dumplings, Three Dumplings, Three Dumplings.
Kuzutsuroku
Dumpling dumpling dumpling dumpling dumpling dumpling
They were popular, too.
I didn't know that.
By the way, the next year was 2000.
That's the year Mariko was born.
First, Uniqlo.
Oh!
Uniqlo.
Even now.
We're still expanding big time.
So, you know...
The generation around Mariko's mom and dad...
I think that's probably the case.
They were born when UNIQLO was founded.
So I didn't really know what UNIQLO was all about.
I didn't really understand what was going on with UNIQLO.
It was so cheap at the time.It was too cheap at the time.
And the quality was so high!
I was surprised.
Especially your father.
You know, the clothes he usually didn't wear to work.
Everyone had a hard time deciding what to do with them.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
And you don't want it to be expensive.
If it doesn't suit you...
On the other hand, UNIQLO is...
It's cheap.
Say, "Okay.
You know, that school...
What's that?
You know...
Triple Crown of Parents
Whenever there's a "yes" or "yes", all the fathers wear the same Uniqlo down jacket.
The black ones like the light ultra jackets... everyone wears them... and they're such a big hit.
It's just that they sold so well.
Everyone was wearing them. They're very high quality.
And PlayStation 2!
PlayStation 2 was more popular than the original PlayStation.
PlayStation 2 became more popular than the original PlayStation.
And, in terms of food, I peeled the amagurri.
That bag of food...
It was released in 2000, and it's still around today.
It's funny, I was just thinking about the year I was born.
It's funny. The year of birth is a bit of a shock, isn't it?
Aimode is so old. Suddenly it seems a little old.
I mean, you don't know about Aimode, do you, Mariko?I'm Aimode. Because, Mariko, you don't know what Aimode is.
I don't know. It's just a year different.
I miss Chakumero. It's like the 90's.
It's the 20th century, the last 20th century culture.
In the 21st century, dreams have changed so much.
At that time, computers were still in the home, and people were getting their computers back for 100,000 yen.
A computer cost 100,000 yen. So computers are common now, but back then, they were still expensive.
Laptop computers, too... maybe... not so much. It was around the late 90's, right?
I thought people started to have them in the late 90's. And they were so thick.
My grandpa's was so thick and so big, it wouldn't fit in a bag.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Cell phones are easy to recognize because everyone has one and they're patterned.
So the switch to cell phones was in, what, 2005 or '06?
It was around 2008 or so. I think it was around junior high school that everyone gradually switched to smartphones, from upper elementary school to junior high school.
I think it was in the sixth grade or the first year of junior high school, so it must have been 2010 or something.
But the year 2010 is really like this, but for me it's like a month ago.
For example, if I did it in 2018, it would have been more than 5 years ago, right?
I'm a little surprised to hear that it's been five years since 2018.
I see... no, no, no, no...
There will come a time when people who were born in the 1900s will be looked down upon.
I'm sure... 1900 is a year?
Just a little before the year 2000.
Mariko's not coming... 2000 is too bad...
I'm jealous of 2000. 2000 is so easy to think of.
First of all, it's the best, you know? It's like we've got all the numbers.
0000 was born in a place that only happens once in a thousand years.
And it's the last one in the 21st century.
The most standard specs...
I wish I was born in 1900, in the 1900s.
But there are only two zeros in 1900, so if there's a moon next time, it'll be in the year 3000.
What? Three zeros?Eh, 0-3 is...
That's so cool! That's so cool!
It's the millennium.
Well, while we're going around like that...
Okay, let's hear from you.
Let's see...
First of all, I'd like to talk about your drawings.
You drew a nice picture over there.
The other day, you know, I've been having a lot of hunches lately.
I've been having a hunch lately that there's some kind of cold noodle soup or something. You know, I've had a hunch recently.
It's becoming a regular thing these days, but in the winter, oshiruko is served.
There's one kind of oshiruko that I like.
I unintentionally said, "See, I like oshiruko.
And he was so cute that he drew a picture of me over there.
So he drew a picture of it over there.
Like this.
She looks like an old lady.
Like an older brother.
She looks like Hoshina's mother.
Hoshina's mom looks like this.
She's got a sleek look.
So Daimyo Nago's oshiruko... you like this...
You were so cute... that time Master.
Thank you very much.
And there's something else...
There's a character from the ironclad ship named Sonyan.
I was going to show it to you earlier, but you gave me a pal point, so I got it back.
Thank goodness...
I killed a metal slime.
I leveled up, too.
Yes, well... you sent me Sogonyan.Yes, er... Sawnyan sent me.
Generous Dibiko-san, Yamato City
Thank you very much!
There was a very rare train called "Sonyan Train".
I wonder if it was just one place...
I wonder if it was just one place.
It's just one of those rare trains.
So it's like this.
Oh, so cute!
This is Sonyan.
Oh, it's so cute!
So, Saunyan Tsuri Kawawa...
Wow...
I've been riding iron for a long time, but I've never seen it before.
but I've never seen it before.
So cute!
Maybe it's somewhere in this Sonyan train.
Or...
Like there's only one place.
Maybe something like that.
It's not often you see a Sonyan train because it's so rare.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, there's more.
Oh, this...
I heard there was a sign in the bathroom.
This sign... well... it's amazing.
I heard he used the restroom at a convenience store.
Mr. Shurbaugh Pikari of Nerima Ward, Tokyo.
There was a sign with a lot of pressure.
Pressure?
So I looked at it while I was in the restroom.So I looked at it in the bathroom.
It's like this.
I'm begging you.
Will you listen to me seriously?
I'll listen to you.
Please don't make a mess.
I can't flush that much toilet paper down the drain.
Look me in the eye.
I mean, look at my face.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
The toilet is clogged.
I'm sorry about that. It's true, it's a big problem when it clogs.
You don't really know what's wrong with a toilet or a plumbing system until it breaks.
We'll just have to call the paramedics.
It's a real pain in the ass, isn't it?
Is that the one you use when the toilet clogs up? Isn't that what they do now?
I wanted to do that when I was a kid.
I'm really good at buff-buffing, by the way. Good?
Is it all about momentum? It's important to apply pressure at the right moment.
If something's jammed, if you break one part, it'll collapse.
Hit it.
If you do that, something collapses in some way, and from there, it's hard to just bash it out in one go.
I used to do that at my part-time job.
And there's a quote... I think it was said by a member of EVE...
It's terrible! The language is terrible!
Troy Polamalu from Sakura City, Tochigi Prefecture sent it to me.
When Eevee Naka released her CD in May, there was a quote in an interview with Music Natalie that really stuck out to me.
Please let me email it to you in the quotes section.
It was the day after last year's first announcement and the graduation performance of Hinata Kashiwagi, and she was asked how she was feeling in the process of performing live with the new organization with two new members.
In the interview, the master who was in last week said, "I can't do it.
He said, "There's no way I can do it, so just shut up.He said in an interview, "I can't do it, so shut up.
What? But isn't he cool? I can't do it, so I'll keep my mouth shut.
That's why he asked me if I was okay. Can you really do it?
I can't do it, so shut up!
Cool master!
She's like a Kyokudo's wife.
By the way...
When the adults around them worried about whether they could surpass the six members' live performance as a new group that is still talked about today...
Shut up! We can do it!
Oh!
You're awesome, Master. You're so cool!
So this is how it's going to be, Master? So this is what it looks like.
Scary!
That's what I'm talking about!
You're so cool! Shut up!
You can't say that in a magazine interview! I can't say it!
If you're Eiichi Yazawa, you know what I'm talking about.
I mean, he's so cool! I love it!
I mean, it's a great quote.
Thank you very much.
It's true, he writes too.
It's amazing.
I know it's a bit rough looking at it on its own face, but...
But as someone who saw the wonderful live performance of the new organization
I felt the unshakable confidence in what we have built and
and the trust in the wild river of the growing Kooyu
and the confidence that comes from having seen Yuna Ima Yuna practicing so hard for this day.
I was deeply moved by her words of confidence.
He said, "I'm so proud of you!
That's right!
The hot master on the stage is a completely different person from the goofy guy who is working part-time.I just wanted to let you know that the hot master on stage is a completely different person than the helter skelter on the part-time job.
I emailed you to let you know that the hot master on stage is a completely different person from the goofy guy he is when he is working part-time.
Oh no, that gap is also there.
I'm not spinning my wheels!
I'm a clunker, but I'm not goofy.
But you said it yourself.
If they know I'm shy, it makes them feel uncomfortable.
So he's always like this.
So far...
I'm not doing this.
Eeeeee!
That's supposed to be a special move.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well...
By the way...
And...
Let's go see what's going on.
Here it comes! Thank you very much.
Thanks to you, creatures, we're alive.
Yes, it's this week... the week of learning about the sea.
I'd like to invite you to reimagine the creatures.
By the way, let me tell you the name of the creature.
Young man!
Like people's names.
Young! Let's play baseball!
Young!
Thank you very much.
Young man!
I'm interrupting something.
I might cheat.
What do you mean, "young man"?What do you mean "young"?
It's true that when you're a master live, it's 180 degrees different.
I used to say it's a 360 degree difference.
No, 360 degrees is back to normal.
I'm trying to say it's totally different.
But I said "360 degrees.
That's right.
So, you're going by car, but it's Impressa.
It's so popular. Impressors, too.
Impressor.
Did you see the high school baseball finals today? Did you guys see the Kanagawa tournament?
It was some kind of cartoonish game.
Yeah.
It was like a cartoon... a comeback at the end of the game.
Amazing.
In the end, it went to Keio High School.
What an amazing game!
Wow!
Ever since the WBC, there's been a lot of godlike games.
That's for sure.
I think they've been influenced by the WBC.
Well, that's why I'm here.
Let's go to Mariko first.
I'm sorry... let's go with Hime.
Hime, please.
Wakashi
Oh!
Yes, yes, it sure sounds like Wakashi.
Wakashi
Looks like a "GUSHIWASHI"!
fish sauce made from fermented grainsjujitsu (classical Chinese dictionary arranged by rhyme, displaying the meanings of kanji and kana)
Birds?
Bird
Is this a bird, or is this a bird by the water?
They are by the water.
I see.
What's that snake-like thing out there?
This is...
It's a rare bird.
It's down there, wow!
Wagashi, wagashi, and here I am. Bang.
Wagashi...
Wait, wait! Wagashi! What?
Let me guess. Let me guess.
What do you think it is? What is it?
Some kind of shell. It's a shell, isn't it? Like a mukagari.
If it's not a mukkari, what is it? The thing under it...
It has eyes. I wonder if they're eyes.
Mr. Lohse. - A chick? The chick from the candy bars? A chick.
It's a tanishi. It says "tanishi" on it.
It says "tanishii" on it. It's stuck to the tank.
I thought it was something like that.
It's true, a pond snail and a pond scorpion look alike.
Something like that...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Everyone, in the sense of the waterfront...
You're almost right.
But "wakashi" means "yellowtail" in Japanese.
Why do yellowtails change their names after birth?
When he was young...
When he was young, his name was Wakashi.When Buri was young, his name was Wakashi.
When he was young.
It's written "fish pressure".
Oh, fish pressure!
Yellowtail is so good, isn't it?
Yes, it's delicious!
But they always look so bad
I always think that when I see yellowtail
It's like, "Oh, no, you can't do this!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm scared of yellowtail.
That's why his mouth is a little down.
Don't say that!
You look bad.
Bad young era, young era, young era...
But she's still young, you know...
By the way, the name of "Buri" changes a lot.
In the Kanto region, there's Wakashi.
It's a child's child, right?
And then Wara-san...
And finally, Buri.
I wonder how people judge them.
For example, what's the difference between "warasan" and "buri"?
Is it the length, for sure?
I wonder what it is, and if there is a standard by which someone decides.
By the way, in Kansai, the names are totally different.
The first one is Mojako.
Wakana
Tubas
Hamachi.
I've heard of hamachi.I've heard of hamachi.
That became the name Mejiro, and eventually Buri.
Mejiro?
Mojako?
It's like a temper with a belly.
Mojaco.
Let's play baseball.
It's all baseball.
Is there a standard?
Centimeter length, just in case.
How many centimeters or how many centimeters are there?
I see... I see... it's hard to remember.
Well, well, well, well... the distribution will be finished soon.
I'd like to thank everyone who sent in their works.
What's today's topic?
Today... today... today...
Today... today... today... today... today... today... today...
You're from around here, aren't you?
I don't know...
You're from Yokohama, right?
Uo-kun? Tokyo?
Ayase, Kanagawa Prefecture.
Yes, he's from around here.
That's right.
That's like Tokyo.
I'd like to meet him once.
Suddenly
But he answers to everything.
We should have a fish contest.
You're so good!Fish, you're so good!
Fish House
You and the master are really good.
I can swim right under your feet.
You're good, aren't you?
We're just boutique clerks.
You work in a boutique?
Boutiques are hard to find.
Do you know what a boutique is?
You know, when we were young.
I don't know how to say it. Fine women's clothing.
And menswear.
I don't know what to say.
There were stores that sold expensive clothes.
You know, the ones that cost more than a regular store, and they were called boutiques.
I think that's French. Boutique way.
I haven't heard that in a long time.
I miss it.
And so...
The live broadcast is about to end.
You don't know why I'm a princess, an admiral, and a watchdog, do you?
You can see what I'm thinking.
Like a master, for example.
I appreciate it when people call me Master because I'm the owner of the store.
But sometimes I want to be called by a different name.
We talked about what we like.
I'm called Admiral.
And Mariko is called Hime.
No, there's a princess among the prawns.
I said I'd like to be called something like that, and they called me Hime.
Do they really call you Hime Hime?Do they really call you "Princess Princess"?
Is that normal?
That's amazing.
What do you want to be called?
Watchdog.
I'm a watchdog.
After all, we have the Admiral and the Princess to protect.
A big dog at the castle gate would be scary.
Will you come in?
I'll take care of it.
I'm not sure.
So, I'll see you all next week for a live broadcast.
Finally, I'd like to leave a message from Mariko.
Have a good week, everybody.
See you next week!